拜托  布洛迪
Come on, Brody.
除了咱俩  大家都去公司派对了
Everyone's at the company party but us.
快走吧
Let's go.
我还要干活
I have work to do.
老兄  曼斯菲尔德说我们可以去30分钟
Dude, Mansfield said that we could go for 30 minutes, and...
我应该20分钟前就告诉你的
I should've told you that 20 minutes ago.
走吧  一定很屌的
Let's go. It's gonna be beast.
你保证再也不说"屌"我就去
Fine, I will go if you promise never to say "beast" again.
走吧
Let's go!
干杯  老兄
Cheers, dog.
好
Okay.
迟来的
It's was, like, a late--
迟来的酒劲
It was a late one.
迟了
It hit late.
这派对真屌
You know, this party is pretty beast.
你刚保证不再说了
You just promised you wouldn't say that.
最后一轮
One last round?
来吧
Let's do it.
我能要杯...
Hey, can I get a...
老兄  我要两杯...
Hey, buddy, I just need two...
我就剩一个月的命了
I have one month to live.
我真想要杯...
I'd really like a...
说你喜欢旧金山49人[橄榄球队]
Tell me you love the 49ers.
-我的确喜欢旧金山49人  -大声点
- I do love the 49ers. - Louder.
我喜欢旧金山49人
I love the 49ers.
天哪  我爱死49人队了
God, I love the Niners.
今年是属于他们的
This is their year.
你要什么
What can I get you?
我要两杯酒  一杯龙舌兰  一杯柠檬糖
I would like to have two shots-- uh, one tequila, one lemon drop.
柠檬糖不是我喝的
The lemon drop's not for me.
我觉得一个男人够自信
I actually think it's kind of sexy
去点女人的酒喝  还挺性感的
when a guy's confident enough to order a girly drink.
边上再多加点糖
Could I have some extra sugar on that rim
再插顶小伞吧
and maybe one of those little umbrella thingies?
我叫布洛迪  在楼上工作
I'm Brody. I work upstairs.
我叫詹妮  在楼下工作
I'm Jenny. I work downstairs.
你就是楼上那些嚣张的
So you're one of those arrogant
全天不停工作的家伙了  是吗
upstairs guys who works, like, 24/7, yeah?
哪有全天不停工作
We don't work that much.
休过假吗
Ever take time off?
这就是了
Yeah ,this is it.
我有15分钟
I have 15 minutes.
这也太没意思了
Well, that doesn't sound very fun.
没想过摆脱这一切吗
Don't you wanna ditch sometimes?
没有吧  没找到合适的理由
I don't know. I never found a good reason to, I guess.
老兄
Bro.
曼斯菲尔德刚群发了邮件
Mansfield sent out a mass e-mail.
他要我们马上回去干活
He wants us all back at work right now.
你怎么看  再来一杯还是...
What do you think? One more drink or...
天哪
Oh, Gosh.
不好说  伙计们
I don't know, fellas.
曼斯菲尔德是那种
Is-- is Mansfield one of those
不介意员工无视他的老板吗
bosses who doesn't mind when you ignore him?
还是那种
Or is he the type of boss
因为你们决定再喝一杯
that would move your desk into the men's room for a month because
忽视他家传的祖业
you decided getting one more drink
而把你们的办公桌搬去男厕所
was more important than the company he built
在那放一个月的老板呢
with the blood of his ancestors?
他就是曼斯菲尔德  对吧
He's Mansfield, isn't he?
太对了
He so is.
很高兴见到你
Nice meeting you.
我也是
You, too.
真好  你醒了
Oh, good. You're up.
你猜怎么着
Guess what?
我妈来这附近了  说想跟我吃早午餐
My mom's in the neighborhood, and she wants to go to brunch.
你也会来的  对吧  她觉得你很帅
You'll come, right? She thinks you're so cute.
我给她发了一张你睡觉的照片
I texted her a picture of you sleeping.
开玩笑的啦  伙计
I'm totally kidding, dude.
你真该看看自己的脸
You should've seen your face.
太搞笑了
That was pretty damn funny.
我得闪了
Um, I gotta bounce.
好的  很随意  我喜欢
Okay. Keeping it casual. Love it.
我们要怎么告别
So how do we say good-bye
而不会感觉这么尴尬和诡异呢
without this feeling so awkward and weird?
昨晚"干"得漂亮
Great work last night?
-是啊  -好
- Hell, yeah. - All right!
门开着还是关上
Open? Closed?
-随意  -好
- Whatever. - Okay.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译：温柔娇妻蓝蓝蓝  妖娆妩媚鸟鸟鸟
时间轴：一家之主森森森   校对&后期&总监：冰蓝
爱情零距离  第一季第一集
三连冠
Yo, threepeat.
继续在丹森信托公司失误吧
Keep dropping the ball on the Danson Trust,
我就能拐走那名客户了
and I'm gonna steal that client.
攻蛋
Ball tap.
只能这样控制住这些年轻人
It's the only way to keep these young guys in check, you know?
我知道你自认为是他们的导师
I know you think you're being their mentor,
但说真的  你只是在捏他们的蛋蛋而已
but really, at the end of the day, you're just grabbin' nuts.
我勾搭的那个女孩还挺不错的
So, uh, that girl that I hooked up with is pretty cool.
她是公司的后勤
She works for the company support staff.
老兄  你勾搭了底楼的妞儿
Dude, you hooked up with a ground floor chick?
是大冒险吗
Was it on a dare?
你对我说三道四
You're judging me,
是因为你带了一张清单
because you carry a list in your pocket
上面写的都是你想与之做爱的东西
of stuff you'd like to have sex with.
看啊
Oh, and look.
你划掉了"大毛绒泰迪熊"
You crossed off "giant stuffed teddy bear".
我们当时在玩具店
We were in a toy store.
你得看看这个
You gotta check this out.
伙计们  快聚过来
Fellas, gather 'round.
这部分很无聊  就是接吻而已
Oh, this part's boring. It's mostly just kissing.
很好
Well, this is good.
我还担心你们会浪费晨会之前的
See, I was worried that you'd all waste the five
这五分多钟
or so minutes before our morning meeting
研究你们的项目书呢
working on your pitch books.
而我却看到你们  说真的
Instead, I see something that, honest to God,
我真想给所有客户看看
I wish I could show to all our clients
我精心挑选来管理他们钱财的人才
the fine young men I picked to manage their money,
正聚在一起  看其中一个人
gathered together, watching one of their brethren
假装跟玩具做爱
pretend to make love to a toy.
莫耶先生  你不参与吗
Mr. Moyer, not participating?
我为泰迪熊黯然神伤  先生
I'm too sad for the bear, sir.
它是"熊熊工坊"的熊  我们能修好它的
Well, he's a build-a-bear, son. We'll be able to fix him.
不过  我说的是周五晚上
Still, I was speaking of Friday night,
你没回来工作
you never came back to work.
这位小凯尔打了你的小报告
Young Kyle here tattled on you.
我知道  凯尔  我保证过不会说是谁告诉我的
And I know, Kyle, I promised I wouldn't tell who told me.
但孩子  我有时会撒谎
But, son, I lie sometimes.
莫耶先生  跟我来阳台谈谈吧
Mr. Moyer, join me for one minute out on the balcony, won't you, please?
来点男人之间的对话吧
Let's, uh, let's spark up some guy talk.
不如由我开始
What do you say? I'll lead off.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
49人队怎么样
How 'bout those Niners?
你喜欢在这里工作吗
Do you like working here?
很抱歉我周五晚上翘班了
I'm sorry that I skipped out on Friday night.
我只是
I just...
-有个女孩...  -是啊
- There was this girl-- - Ah, yes.
这是每一个悲剧故事的开始
The start of every tragic story.
她在底楼工作...
She works on the ground floor--
关于底楼的人有些事你得知道
There's something you need to understand about ground floor people.
他们高中毕业就来这里上班了
You see, they came here right out of high school,
这辈子都坐在
and they're sitting behind the same desk
这一张办公桌后面
that they'll be sitting behind for the rest of their lives.
唯一的出路就是找个像你这样的饭票  莫耶先生
The only way out is to find a meal ticket like you, Mr. Moyer.
她不像是那种人...
Oh, well, she didn't seem like that kind of--
我说完了会给你暗示的  孩子
I'll give you a signal when I'm done talking, son.
现在
Now...
我不想让我最有前途的理财经理人
I refuse to lose my most promising young money manager
陷入一堆个人问题中
to a sea of personal problems.
你下去告诉她一切结束了
You go down, tell her it's over.
客气点  不过要说清楚
Be nice, but be clear.
你现在笑得跟傻子一样
I assume you're grinning like an idiot right now
是因为我刚说"最有前途"了
because I said "most promising" earlier?
是的
I am.
站起来
Stand up.
离开我的阳台以后再欢天喜地吧
Please don't celebrate till you've left my balcony.
难以置信你
I can't believe you slept
跟楼上那种无情的家伙滚床单了
with one of those soulless upstairs guys.
我的一夜情闹钟响了  行吗
My one-night stand alarm went off, okay?
我只允许自己半年这么做一次
I only let myself do those biannually.
我当时情绪很不正常
I was in a weird mood.
我妈把我从小长大住的屋子卖了
My mom sold the house I grew up in.
在哪的
Where was it?
四处跑
Everywhere.
是辆房车
It's an RV.
我以前会把我家开去高中  太酷了
It was cool sometimes I used to drive my house to high school.
你呢  德里克
How about you, Derrick?
派对上勾搭到妹子了吗
You hook up at the party?
我勾搭了一个古巴翘臀妞
Oh, man, I got me a little Cuban chick.
魔鬼身材
Slammin' bod.
奶头堪称一绝  伙计
I mean, she had some fiesta titties, man!
真好  她叫什么
Sweet. What's her name?
我骗你的
I didn't meet nobody.
你不是不会再一直讲大话了吗
I thought you were gonna try to stop lying all the time.
我就是忍不住要说第一个谎
Yeah, man, I can't stop the first lie.
我这人就这样
That's just who I am.
不过詹妮让我在别人
Jenny's making me work on coming clean
继续提问时说出真相
if somebody asks a follow-up question, though.
所以别再问了
So please, no follow-up questions.
你弟没给我们拿到季后赛的票子吧
So I take it your brother's not getting us playoff tickets?
不  他当然拿到了
No, dude, he's definitely gonna get the tickets.
他真的拿到了吗
Is he really getting the tickets?
当然是假的
Hell, no, man!
布洛迪
Brody!
我之前都不知道这下面有办公室
I didn't even know there were offices down here.
好热
Wow, it's hot.
是啊  因为整栋楼的
Oh, yeah, that's 'cause all
电力设备都在这后面
the building's electrical equipment's back there.
我很肯定我们都生不出孩子了
I'm pretty sure none of us can have babies.
我想解释一下那晚的事
Look, I wanted to explain something about the other night.
别担心
Don't sweat it, okay?
每个人在床上都有怪癖
Everybody's got weird sex stuff.
我喜欢眼神接触
I like eye contact,
而你喜欢射了之后喊一声"耶以"
and you like to yell "Yahtzee!" when you finish.
怎么了  我忍不了
What? I can't help it.
我一有性趣就会喊"耶以"
I say "Yahtzee" when get turned on.
大伙儿
Hey, guys.
抱歉迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
昨晚我跟我的基友出去跳舞
Last night I was out dancin' with my gays till...
跳到现在
well, now.
去换工作服
Changing to my work clothes.
这是楼上的家伙吗
Is this the upstairs guy?
你看着像个傻逼
You look like a tool.
友好点
Be nice.
好吧
Okay.
你看起来像个傻逼哟
You look like a tool!
好多了
All better.
爽呆了
Ooh, that was awesome.
抱歉  我应该告诉你我在里面的
I'm sorry. I should've said I was in there.
是我不对
That's my bad.
无所谓了
Whatever, man.
很高兴我终于来上班了
I'm just glad I'm finally at work.
得睡会儿
Gotta get some sleep.
好了  我就是想...
Anyway, I just wanted to ta--
后勤部
Building support.
来吧
Come on.
我们出去聊一会儿
Let's step outside, chat for a second.
不用了  伙计
No thanks, man.
来吧
Aw, come on.
透露点詹妮的事给你
I'll give you the scoop on Jenny.
喜欢这招啊
Oh, he liked that.
兄弟们  要不要雪茄
Hey, fellas. Uh, anybody want a cigar?
太恶心了
That's disgusting.
确定不要
Are you sure?
这是天上掉下来的雪茄
They are falling from the sky.
还点着呢
Oh! Still lit.
也就是说是刚掉下来的
That means it's fresh.
现在告诉你詹妮的事
Now here is the scoop on Jenny.
离她远点
Stay away from her.
她爱我
She loves me.
我们现在处于恋爱中的神奇时刻
We're just in that magical time
而且她还不知道咱俩在恋爱
in a relationship before she knows she's in one.
你和詹妮还会做什么想象中的事
What other imaginary things do you and Jenny do together, huh?
海边漫步吗
You go on long walks by the ocean?
还是去那种DIY酸奶店
Go to one of those build-your-own-yogurt places,
她在鼻子上放颗樱桃
and then she puts a cherry on her nose?
你再一口吃掉  但这样又太冷了
You bite it off, right? But now you're too cold.
所以你们又去咖啡店了
Now you guys go to that coffee hut.
你点了豆奶拿铁
You get your soy latte on, right?
因为她有乳糖不耐症
Because she can't digest dairy.
然后你说"我爱你  亲爱的"
And then you say, "I love you, honey."
她凝视着你的双眸
And she looks right back at you.
然后怎么样
And then what happens?
淡定点  哈佛生
Calm down, Harvard.
你怎么知道我是哈佛毕业的
How'd you know that I went to Harvard?
他叫我呢  小帅哥
Uh, he was talking to me, fancy pants.
我们叫他"哈佛生"  因为他上过大学
We call him "Harvard" 'cause he went to college.
一所很有竞争力的社区大学
A very competitive community college.
那是24个月的课程  而我22个月就完成了
It's a 24-month program, and I actually finished it in 22.
你要谈什么
So what'd you need to talk about?
我是想跟你私下谈谈的
I was actually hoping to do this a little more privately.
"私下谈谈"
"Do this more privately."
周五晚上很棒
Friday night was great,
你真的很贴心  但是...
and you're a really sweet girl, but...
你带美瞳了吗
Do you wear colored contacts?
你的眼睛好蓝
They're so blue.
管他呢
The hell with it.
我们处得很开心
We both had a great time.
应该再一起出去玩
We should go out again.
不了  谢谢  不过谢谢你的邀请
No, thanks. But thank you for asking.
你刚才真的拒绝我了吗
Did you seriously just turn me down?
是的  我们都听到了
Yeah, she did, and we all heard it.
所以  拜拜了您啊
So... Good-bye!
我不会跟楼上的人约会的
I would never date an upstairs guy.
我老板说你们这种人的梦想
My boss told me it was like your dream
就是和像我这样的男人约会
to date a guy like me.
你和老板闲来无事  讨论我们想跟谁约会吗
So you and your boss sit around and talk about who we want to date?
我就说楼上的人根本不做事的
I told you they don't actually do anything up there.
买  买  卖  卖
Buy! Buy! Sell! Sell!
你新买的马怎么样了
Hey, how's your new horse?"
不是每个人都有马的
We don't all have horses, man.
证明啊
Prove it.
我不知道要怎么证明我没有马
I don't know how to prove I don't have a horse.
布洛迪  这真的与你无关
Look, Brody, it's really not about you, okay?
就是你们楼上的人好像都有些
It just seems like you upstairs guys are just kind of, um...
可悲
sad.
可悲  什么
Sad?! What?!
哪里可悲了
How are we sad?
也许是因为你太吵了
Maybe you're sad 'cause you're so loud.
感觉你们从不玩乐
It just seems like you never have any fun, you know?
我们工作是很辛苦  但是在这里
I mean, we work hard, but down here, it's just...
没那么紧张  你明白吗
It's not as uptight, you know?
比如来了一首好歌
Like, if a great song comes on...
*我们要跳舞休息  你知道吗*
*We're gonna have a dance break, you know*
*布洛迪  你知道吗*
*Brody, do you know*
*你知道吗  知道吗  布洛迪你知道吗*
*Do you know? You know? Brody, do you know*
好讨厌  行了  耶以
That's very unpleasant. Okay. Yahtzee.
抱歉
Sorry.
别人开心你就不开心吗
Did you get mad because all the people seemed happy?
你真是个可爱的呆子
You're a cute little nerd.
我要回去工作了
I'm gonna go back to work, okay?
快骑着马儿回去吧
Yeah, why don't you ride your horse back?
老子要杀了你
Hey, I will kill you!
跳舞休息  伙计
Dance break, man!
-要不要一起来  -不要
- You want in on this? - No.
-不要吗  -不要
- No? - No.
*三连冠  三连冠  走在街上*
*Threepeat, threepeat, on the street*
*三连冠  冠呀么冠呀么冠冠冠*
*Threepeat, peat, peat, on the repeat, peat, peat*
*三连冠  三三三连冠*
*Threepeat, three, three, threepeat*
我就叫这名字
That's my name.
-好  -好了  停下
- Okay. - Okay, stop!
这里是办公场所好吗
This is a place of business, man.
拜托  哥们
Oh, come on, man!
陪布洛迪跳超屌的舞蹈  给人家点乐子啊
Fun brody up in this beast!
别工作了  出去吧
Let's ditch work and get outta here.
去哪儿呢  莫耶先生
And go where, Mr. Moyer?
去那间更容易工作的房间
Uh, to that room where it's easier to work.
特殊工作房
The special workroom.
请到我办公室来
My office, please.
自动开门
Automatic door remote.
真是太屌了  先生
That's very beast, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
给你一小时想个新的口头禅
You have one hour to come up with a new word.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
真的抱歉
I'm really sorry.
-我只是  -看见我在办公室里贴的这些词了吗
- I just-- - See all these words that I've posted around the office?
有没有想过我为什么偏偏挑了这几个词
Do you ever wonder why I picked those particular words?
因为这些词是你希望我们拥有的品质吗
Because they're all qualities that you would like us to have?
不是
No.
是因为我用这些词来描述自己
It's because they're all words I use to describe myself.
而且我发现那样很...
And I find that...
让人印象深刻
impressive.
来
Come.
先生  楼下的姑娘搞昏了我的头
Sir, that girl downstairs messed with my head.
跟她讲话就像喝龙舌兰一样
Talking to her is like drinking tequila.
前一秒钟  你还觉得一切都在你掌握之中
One second, you think you're totally in control.
接下来你就发现自己光着躺在院子里
And then the next thing you know, you wake up naked in the yard,
而你妈妈一直说你毁了圣诞节
and your mom keeps saying that you've ruined Christmas.
这姑娘害我质疑我整个人生
This girl's got me questioning my whole life.
你给自己找了个生活复杂者  对吧
You got yourself a life-unraveler, don't you?
那姑娘说的话
That's a girl who says things that
让你从全新  大部分是消极的角度看待生活
makes you look at your life in a whole new and mostly negative way.
是啊
Yes.
她让我觉得我的生活很空虚  我光顾着工作
She made me feel like my life is empty, that all I do is work.
我说不好  也许她是对的
I don't know. Maybe she's right.
也许我没尽情玩乐
Maybe I'm not having any fun.
你觉得我有尽情玩乐吗  莫耶先生
You think I have fun, Mr. Moyer?
你在国庆节烧烤上喝了个烂醉
Well, you got drunk at the 4th of July barbecue,
而且你和你妻子在充气城堡上做爱
and you and your wife had sex in the bouncy castle.
我真爱美国  莫耶先生
I love America, Mr. Moyer.
孩子  我富得流油
Son, I am crazy rich.
我一周上三天班
I work three days a week.
五年来我都没错过我女儿的排球赛
I haven't missed my daughter's volleyball game in five years.
只要我想  就带我的家人去度假
And I take my family on vacation whenever I want to.
你知道我为什么拥有那一切吗
And do you know why I have all of those things?
因为我在四十岁之前真的拼死命了
Because I literally busted my ass until I was 40.
当然  底楼的人们现在很享乐
And sure, some of these ground floor people have fun now,
但十年后他们会怎样
but where are they gonna be in ten years?
一事无成  想尽办法交房租  前途无"亮"
Nowhere. Struggling to make rent with no future.
我现在告诉你
And I'm telling you right now,
那可不如海滨别墅好玩
that's not as much fun as a beach house.
或是一匹马
Or a horse.
我真不敢相信我让那姑娘玩弄了我
I can't believe I let that girl twist me up.
以后不会了
But no more.
你知道你是什么吗  先生
You know what you are, sir?
你是生活解谜者
You're a life-raveler.
对  我就是
Yes, I am.
这句话绝对要上墙啊
And that's damn sure going up on the wall.
先生  你让我找一个"屌"的替换词
Sir, in regards to finding a replacement word for "Beast,"
你觉得"帅呆了"怎么样
what are your thoughts on "Fandango?"
我非常喜欢
I like that a great deal.
我想告诉你们所有人
I would like to let you all know
我不会再来了
that I will not be coming back here anymore.
哈哈
Ha ha.
我觉得现在你下来的次数比我们都多了
I feel like at this point you're down here more than we are.
好啊  楼上的悲剧男
Hey, sad upstairs dude.
你们知道吗
You know what?
我可不悲剧
I am not sad, okay.
你们知道谁的生活很可悲吗  你们的
You know whose lives are sad? Yours.
你们都在一直假装你们很开心
You all keep pretending you're happy,
我现在要去楼上建筑我的未来
and I'm gonna go upstairs and build my future
得到我的海滨别墅  因为显然那些都很有趣
and get my Beach House, because apparently they're very fun.
真好真好真的好
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
这位"希望有我的络腮胡先生"觉得他比我们都强
Mr. Wishes-he-had-my-beard thinks he's better than all of us.
我穿上一套西装  明天就能干你的活儿
I could put a suit on and do your job tomorrow.
我今天就能做
I could do it today,
但我得先找我爸爸借套西装
but I would need to borrow a suit from my dad first.
好了  听完了最后一句疯话
Okay, and on that final insane note,
我现在要说再见了  终于解脱了
I will now say good-bye and good riddance.
这什么眼神  你为什么这样看我
What is that look? Why are you giving me that look?
我真的很担心你会为你刚才所说的话
I'm just really worried that you're gonna feel bad
觉得难过
about the stuff you just said,
我想让你知道  我原谅你
and I want you to know that I forgive you.
别问她问题了  布洛迪
Stop asking her questions, Brody!
你经常和自己说话啊
You talk to yourself a lot.
无视她
Ignore her.
我知道我这么晚还过来有些诡异
I know it's weird, me coming here this late.
不  詹妮  一点也不诡异  我也一直在想你
No, Jenny, it's not weird at all. I can't stop thinking about you either.
我来是因为我把围巾落这儿了
I just came 'cause I left my scarf.
好好好  快请进
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Come on. Come on in.
没问题
Sure, sure, sure.
太棒了  你找到了
Oh, good. You found it.
是啊  回头见
Yeah. See ya.
除非我先见到你  姑娘
Aw, not if I don't see you first, girl.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
-好吧  -行啊
- Okay. - Sure.
冷静
Yeah, peace!
我说  "我唯一乘坐商用飞机的可能性
And I said, "The only way I'm flying commercial is
就是他们为私人飞行拍摄广告
if they're shooting a commercial about flying privately."
commercial既有商用飞机也有广告的意思
这家伙懂我的梗
This guy gets it.
新来的是谁
hey, who's the new guy?
他刚来这里上班
He just started here.
从高盛投资公司过来的
Came over from Goldman.
我们今天尽量做到最好的自己吧
Let's try to be the best version of ourselves out there today.
好吗  哥几个
All right, fellas?
毕竟我们玩的不只是钱
I mean, after all, it's not just money we're playing with.
还有人们的性命
It's also people's lives.
那是个玩笑  我不知道你们这么愤世嫉俗
That's a joke. I didn't realize how cynical you all are.
你们坏透了  你们简直是坏人
You're horrible. You're actually horrible people.
新来的
Hey, new guy.
我可以和你去走廊聊一聊吗
Can I actually talk to you out in the hallway, please?
什么事  头儿
What's the problem, chief?
你感受到了
Do you feel...
我的威胁吗
threatened by me?
我明白
I get it.
一直要做到最好压力很大
It's a lot of pressure having to be the best all the time.
你爸妈是亚洲人
You've got Asian parents.
你懂我的意思
You know what I'm talking about.
你什么时候在高盛投资公司做的
Hey, uh, when were you at Goldman?
我在那待了两年  不记得你啊
I was there for two years. I don't remember you.
抱歉  我们需要立马谈谈
You know what? Sorry. We actually need to talk right now.
行啊
Okay.
看来他想带我去看看他的马
Guess he wants to show me his horse.
关于压力  他说得对
He's right about the pressure, you know.
我父母还逼我上小提琴课
My parents still make me take violin lessons.
我什么时候才能称他们的心啊
When will I ever be good enough for them?
攻蛋
Ball tap.
他们完全信了
They totally bought it.
天啊  我觉得生机"勃"发
God, I feel alive.
我好像勃起了
I think I have an erection.
真的哎
Yes, I do.
你意识到那样有多蠢吗
Do you even realize how dumb that was?
曼斯菲尔德一进来  你就立马会被炒掉
The second Mansfield came in, your ass would've been fired.
总比不上亲一个站在那儿的女孩蠢吧
Well, it's not as dumb as kissing a girl
她甚至都没有回吻你
who just stands there and doesn't even kiss you back.
詹妮不止是站在那儿
Jenny didn't just stand there.
她回吻我了
She kissed me back.
等等
Wait.
她回吻我了
She kissed me back.
现在软了
Well, it's gone now.
你回吻我了
You kissed me back.
什么
What?
你的嘴唇动的程度和我的一样
Your lips moved just as much as mine,
你的舌头在到处乱搅
and your tongue was everywhere.
我的舌头只是在躲你的舌头
My tongue was just hiding from your tongue.
真的吗
Really?
在我的嘴里躲藏吗
It was hiding in my mouth?
那真是个糟糕的躲藏地点
That's a bad hiding spot
因为我的舌头马上就找到它了
because my tongue found it right away.
你就直接承认你回吻我了呗
Will you just admit that you kissed me back?
我当然回吻了你  布洛迪
Of course I kissed you back, Brody.
我有礼貌
I'm not rude.
如果别人吻了我  我总是会回吻
If somebody kisses me, I always kiss back.
詹妮  我们可以去小房间里谈谈吗
Jenny, can I talk to you in the closet for a second?
你就是不能承认我们有交流  对吧
You can't admit it, can you, that we connected?
我只是想拿回我的围巾
I just wanted my scarf back.
你在晚上十一点要围巾干嘛
What did you want with a scarf at 11:00 at night?
怎么  你是围巾警察吗
What are you, the scarf police?
你知道我怎么想吗
You know what I think?
我觉得你喜欢我
I think you like me.
我觉得你喜欢我很成功
I think you like that I'm successful.
我觉得你喜欢我坦诚
I think you like that I'm honest.
但我不是那种你觉得自己该喜欢的男人
But I'm not the guy that you think you're supposed to like,
所以你很纠结
and that's got you all twisted up.
这是事实  我俩都知道
And that's the truth, and we both know it.
你过生日  今晚要做点什么好玩的事吗
Are you doing anything fun for your birthday tonight?
你怎么知道是我生日
How'd you know it was my birthday?
我们在一起的第一晚
Um, the first night that we got together,
我翻了你的钱包
I looked through your wallet.
拿走一些钱  我就那样
Taking some cash. I do that.
我想不起你的名字  所以我看了下你的执照
I couldn't rember your name, so I looked at your license.
"卡罗尔"这中间名可真娘  哥们
"Carol" is a rough middle name, bro.
在你生日那天
Well, on your birthday,
曼斯菲尔德带你出去吃牛排  喝威士忌
Mansfield takes you out for steak and scotch.
不错啊  好玩吗
Cool. Is that fun?
这是强制性的
Well, it's kind of mandatory.
就像一年去看一次牙医
It's like going to the dentist once a year.
你去看牙医
You go to the dentist.
我们知道  少炫耀了
We get it. You know, quit bragging.
你上次过生日时做了点好玩的事是什么时候
Well, when was the last time you did something fun for yo birthday?
那个
Well...
在我18岁的生日时
on my 18th birthday,
在我爸爸过世之前
right before my dad passed away,
他带我去了一家钢琴酒吧
he took me to this piano bar.
他偷偷带我进去
He snuck me in.
让我喝了几瓶啤酒
He let me have a few beers.
他整晚都在弹奏艾尔顿·约翰[英国歌手]的歌曲
And, uh, he played Elton John songs all night on the piano.
我还唱了其中一支  大家都跟我合唱
I actually sang one of them, and, uh, everyone joined in.
真的很棒
It was really awesome.
听起来也很棒
Sounds really awesome.
我们下班后要去街上的潜水酒吧
We go to that dive bar up the street after work.
你该和我们一起去
You should come with us.
是啊  和我们一起去  玩一玩
Yeah, come with us. Have some fun.
-来吧  哥们  -出去逛逛
- Come on, man. - Get on out.
不去也行  要是你很忙
Or don't, you know, if you're busy.
我不能去  我没得选择
I can't. Uh, it's not really my choice.
如果你改变主意了  我们六点出发
If you change your mind, we leave here at 6:00.
布洛迪  等等
Hey, Brody. Wait.
关于你爸爸的那件事...
That, uh, that thing about your dad...
今晚别来
Don't come tonight.
今晚要吃生日牛排  喝威士忌
Oh, birthday steaks and scotch tonight.
谁准备好了  小伙子们
Who's ready, boys?
我们打算先做完
We're just gonna finish this
利率投影的设计概要
client brief on interest rate projections...
然后我们就出发
and then we will head out.
在自己的生日派对上迟到
Going late to his own birthday party.
女士们  先生们  布洛迪·莫耶回归正轨了
Ladies and gentlemen, Brody Moyer is back on track.
你们知道为什么吗
And do you know why?
生活解谜者
不用谢
You're welcome.
这张桌子边少了三把椅子
There's, like, three chairs missing from this table.
这些椅子棒极了
These chairs are fantastic!
你感觉好像要摔倒了  但其实不会
It's like you're about to fall, and then you don't.
就像  天啊  我没事
Like, oh, my god! Oh, I'm fine.
好了  六点过二十了
All right, it's 20 after.
我们该走了  因为他不会来了
That means it's time to go because he's not coming.
我只是  我想再等一会儿
I just--I wanna wait a little bit longer.
如果我们等得太久
Look, if we wait too long,
那个觉得我很萌
the bartender who thinks I'm cute
用我抱抱换他饮料的酒保就会走了
and trades me drinks for hugs is gonna be gone,
调酒的就是那个女酒保了
and then the girl bartender's gonna be there.
好吧  我们可以走了
Okay, fine. We can go.
这家伙有什么重要的啊
What's the big deal about this guy anyways?
他只是另一个无情的楼上傻逼
He's just another soulless, upstairs tool.
不
No.
他很善良啊  他救了你
He's got a soul, man. He rescued you.
其他人会
All those other guys would've
让你被炒掉  然后嘲笑你
let you get fired and then laughed at you.
也许吧  也许他有点善良
Well, maybe. Maybe he has a little bit of soul.
德里克  走吧  托丽都走了
Yo, Derrick, let's go! Tori's already gone.
什么  真的吗
What?! Really?!
*祝你生日快乐*
*Happy birthday to you*
他们在对谁唱歌呢
Who are they singing to?
*生日快乐  亲爱的布洛迪*
*Happy birthday, dear Brody*
*祝你生日快乐*
*Happy birthday to you*
他们都不知道我不在
They don't even know I'm not there.
真抱歉  哥们  别难过
I'm sorry, man. Don't be sad.
我等下用小提琴给你拉生日快乐歌
I'll play it for you later on my violin.
我去拿几瓶啤酒
I'll grab some beers.
谢谢  我不要了
No, thanks. I'm good.
如果我有儿子  他可能也会那样
You know, if I had a son, he'd probably be just like that.
你说什么  先生
Excuse me, sir?
没什么
Nothing.
只是很有意思
It's just interesting.
有时候年轻人会无视你的愿望
Sometimes a young man can ignore your wishes,
然后你反而更尊重他
and you end up respecting him more.
美食精神
好了  好了
Okay. All right.
留着下次再抱吧
Save a little for next time.
好
All right.
他居然来了
No way! He came!
-你好  卡罗尔  -生日快乐  布洛迪
- Hey, Carol! - Happy birthday, Brody!
谢谢
Thank you.
我就知道你会来
I knew you would come.
你不知道
No, you didn't.
如果我不知道  为什么我让他们搬出旧钢琴呢
If I didn't know, why did I have them bring the old piano out?
还记得吗  上次那个过得开心的生日
You remember? The last time you had fun on your birthday.
记得  但那架钢琴一直在那里  对吧
Yeah, but that piano's here all the time though, isn't it?
你以前来过这里吗
Have you ever been here before?
-没有  -那就不是
- No. - Then no, it's not.
上吧  德里克  来
You're up, Derrick. Let's go.
来吧
Here we go.
等等  你会弹钢琴吗
Hold on a second. You can play piano?
不会
No.
但我能弹点东西
But, you know, I can do a little somethin' somethin'.
-那是艾尔顿·约翰的歌  对吧  -是啊
- That's Elton John, isn't it? - Yes.
你该跟着唱啊
So you should sing.
不不  那太荒唐了
No, no. That's ridiculous.
快来唱吧
Yes! Come on!
上去吧
Get up there!
各位  我真的不想成为关注的对象...
Guys, I really don't like being the center of--
*你能告诉所有人*
*And you can tell everybody*
*这是你的歌*
*This is your song*
*也许很简单  但是*
*It may be quite simple, but...*
*现在已经成曲*
*Now that it's done*
*我希望你别介意*
*I hope you don't mind*
*我用语言表达*
*That I put down in words*
*生活有多么美好*
*How wonderful life is*
*因为有你在其中*
*Now you're in the world*
他唱得好烂
He's horrible.